Dimas Prasetyo

https://github.com/DimasPra27 • +62-859-3523-0014 • dimasprasetyo2708@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dimaspra27/

SUMMARY

I am a software engineer with 4+ years of experience in developing and implementing software solutions. My career began at Bina Nusantara University, where I worked for 3 years as a full stack developer. Currently, I work at PT Innovation Anak Indonesia (PARKEE) as a Backend Software Engineer. I am passionate about learning new technologies, system design, time complexity, and writing clean code.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, PT. Inovasi Anak Indonesia (PARKEE)

Apr 2022 - Present

- Responsible for maintaining a microservice backend system, Spring Boot based, handling
 production issues by checking sentries and developing a Parkee application to make it
 easier for users.
- Assist the internal finance team by providing necessary data for financial reporting and support the marketing team by supplying data for analysis.
- Collaborate in development with the front end and mobile teams by providing the endpoints needed by the front end and mobile teams.
- Conduct discussions with third-party teams or from other companies to integrate the Parkee application.

Fullstack Developer, Binus IT Division

Mar 2019 - Feb 2022

- Conduct discussions with system analysts to discuss the features that will be created and determine the timeline and story points needed for development.
- Responsible for developing and maintaining the Binusmaya application to help the ecosystem that occurs during lectures at Bina Nusantara University.
- Develop a user-centric frontend interface that adheres to the specified requirements and seamlessly integrate it with backend services to ensure a cohesive and functional system.
- Development and maintenance of a Competency Test Website, which utilizes the ASP.NET Framework. This website will be used to assess employee competency during bootcamps, providing the HR department with a comprehensive summary of employee skills and abilities.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Computer Science

2018 - 2022

Bina Nusantara University

• GPA: 3.48

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web

(Certificate, DICODING 2021 - 2024)

Dicoding Academy

Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula

(Certificate, DICODING 2021 - 2024)

Dicoding Academy

SKILLS & TECH

• Framework: Codeigniter, Spring boot, ASP .NET

• Languages: Java, Javascript, C#, PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS

• Database: PostgreSQL, SQLServer, MySQL

• Others: GIT Version Control, Redis